stormpulse.com 2012-10-24

# Privacy Policy / Stormpulse / Hurricanes, severe weather, tracking, mapping

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Stormpulse we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask for personal information except where necessary to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Stormpulse, LLC (" **Stormpulse** ") operates [stormpulse.com](http://www.stormpulse.com/). It is Stormpulse's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Stormpulse collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Stormpulse's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Stormpulse's visitors use its website. From time to time, Stormpulse may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Stormpulse also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Stormpulse does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Stormpulse's websites choose to interact with Stormpulse in ways that require Stormpulse to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Stormpulse gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [stormpulse.com](http://www.stormpulse.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Stormpulse—by purchasing access to the Stormpulse Advanced service, for example—are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Stormpulse collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Stormpulse. Stormpulse does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Stormpulse may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Stormpulse may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Stormpulse does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Stormpulse discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Stormpulse's behalf or to provide services available at Stormpulse's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Stormpulse's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Stormpulse will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Stormpulse discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Stormpulse believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Stormpulse, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Stormpulse website and have supplied your email address, Stormpulse may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Stormpulse and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Stormpulse takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Stormpulse uses cookies to help Stormpulse identify and track visitors, their usage of Stormpulse website, and their website access preferences. Stormpulse visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Stormpulse's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Stormpulse's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Stormpulse and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Stormpulse may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Stormpulse's sole discretion. Stormpulse encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
